<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Jednoduchá svítilna</string>
    <string name="app_launcher_name">Svítilna</string>
    <string name="camera_error">Přístup k fotoaparátu se nezdařil</string>
    <string name="camera_permission">Přístup k fotoaparátu je potřebný pro správný stroboskopický efekt</string>
    <string name="bright_display">Bright display</string>

    <!-- Settings -->
    <string name="show_bright_display">Zobrazit tlačítko pro jasný displej</string>
    <string name="show_stroboscope">Zobrazit tlačítko pro stroboskop</string>
    <string name="show_sos">Zobrazit tlačítko SOS</string>
    <string name="turn_flashlight_on">Zapnout svítilnu po spuštění</string>

    <!-- Strings displayed only on Google Playstore. Optional, but good to have -->
    <!-- App title has to have less than 50 characters. If you cannot squeeze it, just remove a part of it -->
    <string name="app_title">Simple Flashlight - Bright display &amp; stroboscope</string>
    <!-- Short description has to have less than 80 chars -->
    <string name="app_short_description">A simple modern flashlight with SOS, stroboscope &amp; bright display, has no ads.</string>
    <string name="app_long_description">
        A clean flashlight with an extra bright display, customizable stroboscope and a predefined SOS mode.

        All these functions can be hugely helpful under certain circumstances.

        The Bright display can have its color changed, opening a new world of possible uses. It can come handy in case you want to see your wider proximity without blinding yourself.

        The stroboscope can have its frequency changed, ranging from really fast blinking to occasional ones.

        If this free flashlight is turned on via the app (not widget), it will prevent the device from falling asleep. The strong torch can optionally turn on at launching the app, but it isn\'t mandatory.

        Comes with a 1x1 widget with customizable color and transparency.

        It comes with material design and dark theme by default, provides great user experience for easy usage. The lack of internet access gives you more privacy, security and stability than other apps.

        Neobsahuje žádné reklamy či nepotřebná oprávnění. Má otevřený zdrojový kód a možnost změny barev.

        <b>Check out the full suite of Simple Tools here:</b>
        https://www.simplemobiletools.com

        <b>Facebook:</b>
        https://www.facebook.com/simplemobiletools

        <b>Reddit:</b>
        https://www.reddit.com/r/SimpleMobileTools
    </string>

    <!--
        Haven't found some strings? There's more at
        https://github.com/SimpleMobileTools/Simple-Commons/tree/master/commons/src/main/res
    -->
</resources>
