<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Lihtne taskulamp</string>
    <string name="app_launcher_name">Taskulamp</string>
    <string name="camera_error">Kaamera liidestamine ei õnnestunud</string>
    <string name="camera_permission">Toimiva stroboskoopilise efekti jaoks on vajalik kaamera kasutamise luba</string>
    <string name="bright_display">Kirgas ekraan</string>
    <!-- Settings -->
    <string name="show_bright_display">Näita nuppu ekraanil kirkana</string>
    <string name="show_stroboscope">Näita stroboskoobi nuppu</string>
    <string name="show_sos">Näita SOS-nuppu</string>
    <string name="turn_flashlight_on">Rakenduse käivitamisel lülita taskulamp sisse</string>
    <!-- Strings displayed only on Google Playstore. Optional, but good to have -->
    <!-- App title has to have less than 50 characters. If you cannot squeeze it, just remove a part of it -->
    <string name="app_title">Lihtne taskulamp, mis kasutab kirgast ekraani ja pakub stroboskoobi võimalust</string>
    <!-- Short description has to have less than 80 chars -->
    <string name="app_short_description">Lihtne tänapäevane taskulamp, mis kasutab kirgast ekraani ja pakub SOS- ja stroboskoobi võimalust ning kus puuduvad reklaamid.</string>
    <string name="app_long_description">
        A clean flashlight with an extra bright display, customizable stroboscope and a predefined SOS mode.

        All these functions can be hugely helpful under certain circumstances.

        The Bright display can have its color changed, opening a new world of possible uses. It can come handy in case you want to see your wider proximity without blinding yourself.

        The stroboscope can have its frequency changed, ranging from really fast blinking to occasional ones.

        If this free flashlight is turned on via the app (not widget), it will prevent the device from falling asleep. The strong torch can optionally turn on at launching the app, but it isn\'t mandatory.

        Comes with a 1x1 widget with customizable color and transparency.

        It comes with material design and dark theme by default, provides great user experience for easy usage. The lack of internet access gives you more privacy, security and stability than other apps.

        Contains no ads or unnecessary permissions. It is fully opensource, provides customizable colors.

        <b>Check out the full suite of Simple Tools here:</b>
        https://www.simplemobiletools.com

        <b>Facebook:</b>
        https://www.facebook.com/simplemobiletools

        <b>Reddit:</b>
        https://www.reddit.com/r/SimpleMobileTools
    </string>

    <!--
        Haven't found some strings? There's more at
        https://github.com/SimpleMobileTools/Simple-Commons/tree/master/commons/src/main/res
    -->
</resources>
